<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Cow.006</string>
    <string name="title_activity_rules">Rules</string>
    <string name="game_rules">
    The goal is to be the player with the lowest number of points. To do this, the players should
        try to get rid of their cards, especially the ones with more cattle heads.\n\n
    Cow.006 is played using a special card deck that in the original version has a cattle head in
        the center of the card and a variable number of small cattle heads on the top. The cards are
        numbered 1 to 104, each giving 1, 2, 3, 5 or 7 points (i.e. cattle heads) to the person who
        picks it up.\n\n
    In the deck there are:\n
    - 1 card with 7 cattle heads—number 55\n
    - 8 cards with 5 cattle heads—the multiples of 11, i.e. 11, 22, 33, and so on through 99,
        except for 55\n
    - 10 cards with 3 cattle heads—the multiples of ten, i.e. 10, 20, 30, and so through 100\n
    - 9 cards with 2 cattle heads—the multiples of five which are not multiples of ten, i.e. 5, 15,
        25, and so on through 95, except for 55\n
    - 76 cards with 1 cattle head—the rest of the cards from 1 through 104\n\n
    Preparation\n
    Ten cards are dealt to each player.\n
    Four uncovered cards are arranged on the table to form a vertical line.\n\n
    Gameplay\n
    At each turn, each player selects a card to play, and puts the card face down on the table. When
        all the players have selected a card, the cards are uncovered.\n\n
    Starting with the lowest valued card, and continuing in increasing order, each player must put
        their card at the end of one of the four rows on the table, following these rules:\n\n
    The card must be put on a row where the latest (end) card is lower in value than the card that
        is about to be played.\n\n
    The card must be put on the row where the latest (end) card is the closest in value to the card
        that is about to be played (if your card is 33, then place it next to the 30 not the 29, for
        example)\n\n
    If the row where the played card must be placed already contains 5 cards (the player\'s card is
        the 6th), the player must gather the 5 cards on the table, leaving only the 6th card in
        their place to start a new row. The gathered cards must be taken separated and never mixed
        with the hand cards. The sum of the number of cattle head on the gathered cards will be
        calculated at the end of the round.\n\n
    If the played card is lower than all the latest cards present on the four rows, the player must
        choose a row and gather the cards on that row (usually the row with the fewest cattle
        heads), leaving only the played card on the row.\n\n
    The cards of all the players are played following these rules, from the lowest player card to
        the highest one.\n\n
    At the end of the turn, the players each select a new card to play; this is repeated for 10
        turns until all the cards in the hand are played.\n\n
    End of the game\n
    After the 10 turns, each player counts the cattle heads on the cards gathered from the table
        during the round. The score of each player is collected on the paper and a new hand
        starts.\n\n
    The game ends when a player collects a total of 66 or more cattle heads. The winner is the
        player who has collected the fewest cattle heads.\n\n
    </string>
    <string name="title_activity_setup_solo_game">Setup solo game</string>
    <string name="title_activity_leaderboard">Leaderboard</string>
    <string name="player_count">Player count</string>
    <string name="start_game">Start game</string>
    <string name="bot_level">Bot level</string>
    <string name="bot_number">Bot number</string>
    <string name="play">Play</string>
    <string name="solo">Solo</string>
    <string name="multiplayer">Multiplayer</string>
    <string name="miscellaneous">Miscellaneous</string>
    <string name="game_rules_button_text">Game rules</string>
    <string name="global_leaderboard_button_text">Global leaderboard</string>
    <string name="sign_in_information_text_view_default_text">Signing in&#8230;</string>
    <string name="sign_out_button_text">Sign out</string>
    <string name="title_activity_setup_multi_game">Setup multiplayer game</string>
    <string name="back_to_main_menu">Back to main menu</string>
    <string name="final_scores_activity_label">Final scores</string>
    <string name="waiting_players">Waiting for players…</string>
    <string name="game_start_message_text">The game is starting!</string>
    <string name="next_round_message_text">Prepare for the next round!</string>
    <string name="logged_in_prefix">"Logged in as: "</string>
    <string name="not_logged_in_text">Not logged in: multiplayer and leaderboard features are disabled!</string>
    <string name="loading">Loading...</string>
</resources>
